{
    "subject": "resource/Presley_Hart",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Anaheim,_California",
    "human_readable": "Presley Hart was born in Anaheim, California.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.872879147529602,
            "question": "Where was Presley Hart born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8439747095108032,
            "question": "Is Presley Hart from California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7369361519813538,
            "question": "What year was Presley Hart born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42279303073883057,
            "question": "Are there any other celebrities born in Anaheim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36633455753326416,
            "question": "What state is Anaheim located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28239113092422485,
            "question": "What are some famous places in Anaheim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25952762365341187,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Presley Hart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17348229885101318,
            "question": "Is Anaheim a big city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11307627707719803,
            "question": "What is the weather like in Anaheim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10877632349729538,
            "question": "What kind of activities are popular in Anaheim?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Presley Hart was born in Anaheim, California.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8575_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the weather like in Anaheim?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8575_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Anaheim a big city?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8575_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Presley Hart?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8575_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8575_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8575_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8575_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8575_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8575_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8575_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8575_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8575_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8575_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8575_54.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. All three files with paths ending in \"5.txt\", \"16.txt\", and \"54.txt\" mention that Presley Hart was born on December 1, 1988, and at least two of them (5.txt and 40.txt) specify that she was born in Anaheim, California."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Presley Hart was born in Anaheim, California. Therefore, the statement \"Presley Hart was born in Anaheim, California\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}